finda.co.nz 2018-03-04

# Finda® Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you might provide via any of our websites or mobile applications (each, a “Property”). This policy explains how we manage your information. For the purposes of this policy, “we”, “us” or “our” means Yellow Pages Group Limited (having its registered office at 604 Great South Road, Ellerslie, Auckland) together with its related companies, including Finda Limited.

### Your information

You acknowledge and agree that we may collect information about you. This may be:

  * provided voluntarily by you;
  * obtained or derived from Property usage information (whether through tracking your click behaviour or otherwise);
  * obtained or derived from aggregated data not relating to you personally, such as the measuring of traffic relating to our Properties; and/or
  * provided by third parties.

You may decide whether to provide any information we seek from you. However, if you do not provide it, we may not be able to provide services to you.

### Use and sharing of information

We collect and use your information to:

  * generally operate our business;
  * provide you with, and improve, our Properties, products and services;
  * inform you about our Properties, products and services, and any changes thereof;
  * administer our contests, promotions, surveys and other services;
  * obtain your feedback or views about our Properties, products and services;
  * respond to any queries, feedback or other correspondence from you;
  * gain an understanding of your needs;
  * prevent and detect any misuse of, or fraudulent activities involving, any of our Properties, products or services; and/or
  * maintain and develop our business systems and infrastructure, including testing and upgrading of these systems.

Personal information may be shared with our officers, employees, contractors, agents, professional advisors and joint ventures, and third parties (including our customers or suppliers) in relation to the purposes described above. We take reasonable steps to ensure that any third parties are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.

We may also share your personal information as required by law, court order, regulatory authority or the listing rules of any stock exchange, to exercise our legal rights, or to defend against legal claims.

We will generally collect and use non-personal information to:

  * provide our customers or suppliers with marketing or promotional materials regarding our products and services; and/or
  * assist our staff in providing tailored sales offers to our customers.

### Holding and correcting personal information

Under the Privacy Act 1993 you have rights of access to and correction of personal information that we hold, where such information can readily be retrieved. We reserve the right to require payment of our reasonable costs in relation to the access to and correction of certain information.

To protect your privacy and the privacy of others, we may have to verify your identity before we can give you access to, or change, information about you.

### Links to other websites

Our Properties may provide links to other websites. Please note that these websites may have different security and privacy policies. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for any information that you divulge to these websites or how those websites or the organisations that own and manage those websites collect, use or disclose such information.

### Use of cookies

Information about the use of our Properties is of commercial value to us. To help us provide the best possible services via our Properties for users and our customers, we may collect and store information about the way our Properties are used (such as the number and type of electronic devices connecting to each Property, the location and any unique IDs provided by those devices, the operating systems and browsers used by those devices, and which parts of our Properties are being viewed or used). This may include sending a “cookie” to your device. A cookie is a message given to an internet browser by a web server. The browser stores the message in a text file. The message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This identifies your device uniquely but does not harm your device and does not identify you.

Our websites use one type of cookie for reporting on the use of the website, and another type of cookie to provide you with certain website functionality (such as displaying content more relevant to you, or enabling you to retain search queries). Cookies will be sent to your device the first time you visit one of our websites. If you do not wish to have a cookie placed on your computer, please visit <http://info.yellow.co.nz/optout.html>. Alternatively you may be able to disable all cookies via your browser’s “Options” or “Preferences” menu.

### Advertisements

We may use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you use our Properties. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your use of our Properties in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving such advertisements, our third-party advertiser may place or recognise a unique cookie on your device. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by this company, please visit <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy>.

### Nielsen//NetRatings

We use the Nielsen//NetRatings counting system to help us improve our services by tracking common entry and exit points for our Properties, compiling anonymous information about usage of our Properties, and randomly and anonymously surveying users of our Properties. To do this, our Properties may include a small piece of code (for example, on each web on each page) which accumulates these statistics. For more information and to view Nielson//Net Ratings’ privacy policy, please visit <http://www.nielsen-online.com/corp.jsp?section=leg_prs>.

### Security

Although we use safeguards to protect your personal information against theft, loss or unauthorised access, use, modification, disclosure or disposal, as no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure, we cannot ensure and do not warrant the security of information you transmit or receive through our Properties. These activities are conducted at your own risk.

### Emails

By registering an account with us via any of our Properties or by otherwise providing us with your email address, you consent to the receipt of commercial emails from us or on our behalf, or from our related companies and/or certain third parties (unless you expressly deny such consent at the time of registration or provision). You may opt-out of receiving commercial emails at any time by using the unsubscribe facility provided in each commercial email or in certain of our Properties. We may always send you non-commercial emails.

### Terms of Use

Our [Terms of Use](http://support.finda.co.nz/terms-of-use/) apply in addition to this Privacy Policy. In the event of any conflict between this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, the Terms of Use prevail to the extent permitted at law.

### Changes to this policy

We may change this policy, by adding, changing or removing terms at any time. Any change applies from the time it is published on the relevant Property. You should check from time to time to see if this policy has changed.

### Contact Details

If you have any questions about the privacy of your personal information please [contact us](http://support.finda.co.nz/contact-finda-co-nz-helpdesk/).
